# KINSLERT DANIEL VIRGUEZ

Venezuela, Araure - portuguesa +584245857047 dkinslert@gmail.com

## Objetive

Set strategies to achieve the objectives as vision between the assigned roles, evaluate the necessary information between the competition and the product to be made in the market, technologies, maintain communication between the necessary aspects improving strengths and weaknesses before participation, and thus with the necessary skills to create said service

### **Skills**

Experience in applications based on frontend. Good management of third-party libraries and frameworks based on javascript and php, understanding of the development environment and mvc pattern applied to the frontend architecture, good experience and skill over angular 1.x - latest, and on the nodejs platform. third-party library management. browserify, jquery. mapping of relational objects applied to database, use of console and cli in lamp environment. gulp, bower, browserify, babel-cli, babel-node, ecmascript, typescript, vuejs, reactjs, react native, swift. relational and non-relational database and css frameworks and preprocessors. Windows and linux operating systems. other tools Jira, slack, git

# Experience

Software developer, Compuweb. J.A 09-06-2016 – 12-11-2016

- Frontend software developer
- Wordpress, Joomla
- Html5, css3

Software developer, Corporación Eureka C.A 01-02-2016 – 07-07-2016

- Frontend Software developer
- Wodpress, Joomla
- Html5, css3
- Admin system, management server Linux (Unix)

# Software developer, Desarrolladorespweb 09-07-2016 – 10-12-2016

- Frontend software developer
- Codeigniter
- Html5, css3

# Software developer, Identidadweb

22-12-2017 - 23-03-2018

- Frontend software developer
- Codeigniter
- Html5, css3

# Software developer, Workana inc 2018

- Partnert developer
- Javascript
- bootstrap

## Education

National university open – systems engineer Platzi – San Francisco, usa – Certification. php con laravel, marca personal, marketing de voz a voz, basic programing.

register number and licences:

Programación básica. 12 de enero de 2018

código: ab91f15d-b800-4933-b442-100246f355c9

Laravel. 25 de enero 2018

código: 1843ec7-5321-4994-9c61-3f3fa9138018

marca personal. 12 de febrero de 2018

código: f2f74a0c-af1b-4375-a02c-4°2e5871e277 Resources of development and design software

online. 29 Noviembre, 2018.

Certificacion Udemy: UC-XEEQJW89

Angular – Progressive Web Application Online, html Certificacion Udemy: UC-1AVQLL7UX 27 Noviembre, 2018

Setup operative system macintosh enviorement development Certification Udemy: UC-8WKP4HV0 4 diciembre, 2018

Programing for languaje Swift Certification Udemy: UC-SYU2NWUF 4 Diciembre, 2018

Workana – Argentina, buenos aires – Certificación – JavaScript avanzado, Bootstrap Básico, JQuery Avanzado

Udacity – new delhi, usa – Curso. angularjs, backbone, ember.

Pluralsight - Boston, usa – Curso. restful service with nodejs unit testing with nodejs

Code school - Boston, usa – Curso. html5 css3 jquery github

#### Comunication

i has received positive and excellent reviews of the projects carried out, in the presence of the participation of each company, he has contributed excellent knowledge with the collaboration of the colleagues, doing great work for each institution in the development of the software, I consider myself an architect, developer of free software technology among software developers

## Management

Among the projects carried out so far, I have participated as a project leader among which I can name Patagonia bank (headings), Argentina, with the participation of Boyer Yender (Software developer), nature Valley with the participation of Carmelo Fallone (Software developer). Receiving excellent reviews for the work done So far, I have had the opportunity to participate as a developer and collaborate in different projects as a software developer and project architect with the php and JavaScript frontend and backend languages also with content manager using WordPress and others

### References

Jose Acurero Compuweb J.A +584149556062

Jose Linarez Corporación Eureka C.A +58 255-6236905

Oswaldo Gonzales
DesarrolladoresPweb
+58 424-1887407

Leandro palacios InmenteWeb +54 11 2060-4776

Joel Pujol JoelPujolDj +54 9 11 2253-9113